Hey y'all and welcome back to Living in
Central Texas. I'm Andrea Dudik here
with my partner and friend Matt [music]
Dick. And today we'll be doing things a
little bit different from our normal
format. But it's going to [music] be
super awesome and super fun.
>> Yep. We got the dash cam rolling, the
phone's rolling, the cameras rolling, we
got everything rolling for real time
drive through [music] three surf
suburbs.
People don't always think about [music]
but should. We're going to be showing
you Nolanville, Troy, and Little River
Academy, giving you a feel of the roads,
the neighborhoods, schools, the
lifestyle, and really everything in
between. So whether you're relocating to
Fort Hood, if you're looking to relocate
for any of the hospitals here in Temple,
whether that's MLAN Children's or Baylor
Scott and White VA Hospital, or really
you're just looking to kind of escape
from [music] city living, this video is
going to be for you.
And then at the end of the video, we're
going to go right into exactly what 400K
[music] buys you in these suburbs. These
are three suburbs you definitely need to
be paying attention to.
And then we have Raquel, who's my
executive assistant and an amazing
realtor in the back seat. So if [music]
you see any peaks of her, she's awesome.
them and that she's back there. Okay, so
it's a little bit gloomy today, a little
bit overcast. The sun should [music] be
peeking its way out it looks like in
about an hour or so. We'll see if that's
true. But
very typical of Texas. [music] If you
are not familiar or from this area, the
weather is really like that.
Can rain one moment and then be rainbows
and sunshine
in no time.
So what we're currently on is 317
[music]
south
>> south. This is kind of the main
thoroughfare [music]
through
Belton Temple.
So, from where we currently are to Troy,
we're looking at about a 20 minute
drive.
>> Oh, and he ran it all the way up.
>> He did. [music]
>> Oh, Brandon's so hungry.
>> He is.
>> So, right now [music] it's 10:00 a.m. on
a Friday afternoon. You can see traffic
[music] is super light.
If you're from bigger cities, [music]
this is pretty typical.
Even after hours or after work hours,
you know, after 4:00 or something, it's
not super busy. I mean, some of these
areas get a little bit more congested,
[music]
maybe adding what, another 5 minutes to
your drive.
>> Yeah.
>> But nothing like those big cities.
It kind of had us routed going up
[music] 317
um through
more rural
roads, but we're going to take you down
[music] West Adams,
which is that main road through Temple,
like coming out of Belton. [music]
very very popular road
but
give [music] you a good feel of the
area.
We actually just got [music] the
Chick-fil-A over here. Everyone was
thrilled about it, including myself. You
>> are you Chick-fil-A guys?
>> Yeah, sometimes.
>> Yeah.
>> Are boys [music] Chick-fil-A?
>> Kids?
>> Yeah, they both are.
>> Yeah.
Raquel, do your kids like Chick-fil-A?
Do you like Chick-fil-A?
>> At least twice a week.
Yeah, genius [music]
model. So, I think if you're interested
in Troy, Matt, what do you think some of
the biggest reasons someone [music]
might want to live in Troy are?
>> Location. Basically, you can just hop on
and then meet in Temple or Waco. That
was really quick for jobs. So whether
you're in the medical profession, some
sort of [music] industry, or um work
have a bad uh Baylor or even UHB.
>> Mhm. Yep.
>> Still have that small town [music] charm
feel
even though
you're [music] relatively close to
everything.
>> So from Troy, you're probably about 10
to 12 minutes out from
touching temple. So you can really,
like Matt was [music] saying, get that
more rural, quiet feel. Plus, they have
lower property taxes than a lot of this
area. [music] So that's really great.
Save on your monthly payments a little
bit,
but [music] be super close to Temple and
all the amenities.
I'd [music] say
really great if you're working at Scott
and White.
>> Yeah. or the VA or MLAN's Walmart
distribution, Sam's distribution.
Whatever happened with the uh the Meta
Complex that [music] were supposed to be
building up
>> I don't know,
>> but there's space too. We've been
getting a lot of people for that
>> out in McGregor.
>> Mhm. And [music] if you Same thing with
Waco. I mean, really what [music] 20
minutes?
>> 20 25 minutes from Waco. I think it's a
uh
depend on how fast you drive down 15 20
minutes. The balor's here on my hospital
building at Temple or and Waco.
>> Yeah. So, straight shot up 35 and you're
in Waco.
So, for someone that's maybe not wanting
to be in Waco, maybe get a little bit
better of a deal cuz you you have to
remember too [music] in you get closer
to Waco or you get in Waco, your home
[music] prices are going to go up.
Generally, your price per square foot is
going to go up just same as if you get
closer to Austin. [music]
So, you can generally get much better
bang for your buck by living in the
Temple, Belton, and suburb area that
we're taking you on a little tour of
today.
>> You're going to take this all the way
35,
>> I think. So,
>> okay.
>> We're just going to [music] show all the
way up, Adams.
>> Okay.
>> Just all the way.
>> [music]
>> That place has been for sale for a long
time. Have you seen it?
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> In other news, we got new t-shirts.
>> Oh, yeah. We got new t-shirts.
>> Mhm.
>> So, we did. [music] We just got our new
boyfriend. Yeah, we got four new colors.
We three were [music] a success. Well,
two and a half. You don't really love
your one color either, I
>> Yeah, [music] I'm going to wear it.
Yeah, black.
We got olive. We got yellow gold. It
looks like sunshine. [music] I'll
probably wear that next week.
>> Yeah, I was going for more of a mustard
yellow. And it's definitely a happy sun,
[music] like mellow yellow.
>> Very mellow yellow.
>> [music]
>> I really like this olive color. Yeah,
olive color. This uh forest emerald
color I'm wearing. Matt's black one
[music] looks great.
Your olive one has like a tannanish hue.
>> Yeah, tan brown.
>> But hey, if you are moving to central
Texas [music] and you would like one of
these t-shirts,
let us know.
come out and look at [music] some houses
and we'll give you a t-shirt.
>> Yeah. All right. So, we're at the uh
West [music] Adams Central. Is it
Central? Yeah, Central and I35
intersection. Um what's cool about this
area is you got like a a lot of fast
places. You got a a couple different
like urgent cares and then you have the
Temple High School that's right here as
well. Um,
the only Black Rifle coffee company
[music] is right here at this
intersection, which is kind of cool. Uh,
and to me, I always find it funny that
these [music] guys put their their
coffee shops next to like other
other coffee places like
>> Oh my gosh, a Roberto's. I didn't know
that was going to Is that Is that new?
>> Huh?
>> That Roberto?
>> I have no idea. They They put it next to
like Dash Bros or Starbucks. [music]
And look, there's another new
Chick-fil-A going in. I didn't know that
was going on.
>> And over on this direction on this side
of Adams, you're you're in True Temple.
So, you're going to be in that Temple
[music] ISD, which where whereas where
we started, even though we [music] were
in we went through Temple, a lot of that
was built in ISD.
Talk a lot about that in our videos cuz
that really is important to a lot of
people. Maybe not some for sure. But
[music] if the school district is
important to you, you belt ISD is more
[music] sought after often than Temple
ISD, which is reflected a lot in our
purchase prices of our homes.
>> And then with the school districts,
really do your homework on it because
more and more by kids are diving [music]
into
our current school district. We're
finding that it's not as glamorous as
everybody thinks it is. So just make
sure you do your homework on your school
districts.
>> Yeah. Everybody's needs are a little bit
different.
Now, Troy ISD that we're headed into,
>> [music]
>> um, I would I've heard really great
things about Troy ISD. I feel like Troy
is one of those places where a lot of
people
actually Troy and Little River, so two
of the places we're visiting today, two
of the suburbs. I would say Troy and
Little River more so are two suburbs
that a lot of people move to and kind of
don't move house like they're really
proud [music] to be in those areas and
stay there.
>> It's uh my understanding it's a lot more
classroom sizes are a lot smaller.
[music]
Uh the communication across the board
from teachers to [music] parents a lot
better. And then I just Googled it. Troy
ISD received a B accountability rating
from the state for 20 to 2024 and 2025
student year.
Um,
>> what's Troy's website? Is it
troyisd.org? [music]
>> troisd.org.
>> So you can head to troic.org [music]
to see specifics. And you can also
always head over to websites like niche.
Is it niche.com?
>> It is niche.com
>> to get specific statistics on school
districts.
>> They have a rating on niche.com of 4.27
[music] out of five.
>> Only niche.com.
[music]
>> Overall B rating.
>> Again, I just Googled it. Troy ISD
um
rating.
>> So again, we are on I35 headed up to
Troy. This is if you were to take it
south, we'd be headed to [music] through
So, Georgetown, Round Rock, Cedar Park,
all those areas into Austin and then
headed north, you would pass obviously
Troy. We've got what? Moody, Lena,
um
Chrisville Eddie, and then the bigger
one being Wayo.
>> Yeah,
Chrisville Eddie.
>> But 10:30 in the morning on a Friday and
this is what traffic looks like. We're
headed out there by typical.
>> Yeah, I'd say I'm pretty serving for a
Friday.
>> Yeah.
>> And just remember, the slow lane is the
far right lane and the fast lane which
is above the speed limit is the far left
lane.
>> You're dropping hands.
>> Are you dropping hands?
>> No. No. You're going the appropriate
speed.
>> It's when you have those individuals cuz
I'm trying not to cuss.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> That are in the far left lane going the
speed limit.
>> Matt and I have a very unique
relationship. Um it's it's glamorant
that our last names mine is dudick and
his is dick. It look like a partnership
made in heaven, but I
am much more proper
and that is about as loyal as you get,
but [music] swears like a sailor
>> like a buzz saw.
>> So, he's trying to remain extra.
>> Although, I don't really cuss a lot in
my videos, I don't think.
>> You know, really don't. You're great.
>> Yeah.
>> Or our editors are just really great at
editing. Really good. Matt's people love
him and my people I think love beast. So
person for every person, you know. And
then there's Raquel who's just
silent little killer.
>> I forgot to mention it, but there's a
bies on our [music] way out of Temple.
So that I would say that's like kind of
like the line for temple [music] is the
bies,
>> even though it's right before.
>> Sorry y'all. And then if we're talking
to our cameras, sometimes we might miss
our exit.
>> I told you to keep GPS on.
>> It's okay. [music] It's fine.
>> But did you die?
>> I did not. I did not die.
>> It's okay.
Um [music]
and then kind of
so you know when you're in Troy is when
you see the LS gas station [music] on
the left. Just make sure you take that
exit. Um, and of course you go up the
hill and then you start building right
into downtown Troy. What is the name of
that restaurant? It's got some yummy mac
and [music] cheese.
>> There's a new mac and cheese bar, I
think, in Hurka Heights, right? We still
haven't gone to it. Is it even new
anymore?
>> I don't know. That's a very [music] good
question.
>> Have you been to it?
>> No.
>> Do you like mac and cheese?
>> No, not really.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Rock Hill is a communist.
Just figure that out.
So Troy is growing. We do have some oh
well quite a bit of new construction
actually happening out here. Um we're
going to be checking out one of the
builders today. I actually did a whole
video on
Troy, Texas specifically. It was also an
overcast day the day that we did that
video. But they've got some really
amazing priced
um sort of [music] town homes for sale
right now.
And
>> yeah, town homes, duplexes,
>> duplexes. That's what I was looking for.
But there are singlesided duplexes. So
if you are like there's currently as of
today there are still homes under
200,000.
>> This is very tragic news. [music]
Oh,
>> I'm trying to look and see if it's
closed or not, but there's a restaurant
right when you pull in. And we're going
to turn left on Main Street and go down
[music] to Turtle Creek, but if you turn
right, there was a restaurant named
[music]
uh the Troy Lumber Company. I don't know
what the name of it is now,
but it's got really good mac and cheese.
[music]
>> That right there.
>> Yes, the green trim building dough
there. Um, [music] but it says it's
permanently closed. cuz I'm not 100%
sure. I think they just changed their
name. Um, but it's it's so [music] good.
So, if you ever you're ever in Troy, go
check it out. Or if you've eaten at
there, what's your favorite dish besides
the mac and cheese? I think I've had one
of their like toasted sandwiches. Those
are really good, too. But the mac and
cheese, loved it.
>> Okay.
So, Main [music] Street, what? West on
Main Street. Is that right?
>> Yes. west on Main Street or at the red
light of the of the access [music] road
in Maine, turn left.
>> We're passing Troy High School [music]
on the left, Maize Elementary. It's our
elementary school here.
And then right next to it is
>> Raymond
Maze
>> Raymond's Maze of Middle School.
>> So, we're in Turtle Creek. Um, I really
love their entry sign, [music] by the
way. Um, that's great.
>> They've got some really wonderful
builders in here, and [music] they're
still building new homes.
>> Mhm.
A good variety of builders. See, you
have homes priced in the 300,000s
up to
what? Mid5sish. [music]
>> [music]
>> So, we're going to take you through
Turtle Creek and we'll be back. You have
me to tell them [music] that or do you
have me to text?
>> Oh, maybe text. Yeah, that's probably
better. You say go right.
>> Yeah, we're going to go right right
here. Okay.
>> Sorry, I got lost in my head.
>> I get it.
Are you hot? You can do all this on your
own, [music] friend.
>> Oh yeah, you can.
>> I'm like super.
>> You can do your own stuff back there.
You want to pull yourself off? Also feel
a little sweaty.
only filing these [music] shirts,
>> right?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh,
Troy does not have a grocery store, so
you have to go to Temple.
>> Yeah,
>> you have to drive 10 minutes.
>> You got to drive 10 minutes to Temple
for a grocery store.
>> Yeah.
>> They got a Dollar General, though. You
can do some light shopping there.
So, nearest medical is going to put you
at temple
again. Super easy shot down 35.
Oh,
>> now we're heading over to Little River
Academy. [music]
>> Little River Academy is just the cutest.
[music]
I saw this little story about how that's
where my husband was born and raised and
his parents are just the sweetest. I got
so lucky with my in-laws and they
moved away from this house that my
husband grew up in and rented it out and
they bought a little house in Belton.
Well, it wasn't a little house. It was a
bigger. It was like twice the size of
that house. And after a year of being in
it, they said, "No, we want to go back
to our Little River home." And tenants
left and they moved back in and they're
back in the house that they've owned for
40ish years and they just love the
community so much. And I feel like
that's pretty common with Little River
that again, people kind of go there and
want to stay there. It's just very small
and quaint, but access to everything is
[music] awesome.
really want.
>> Take the Buck his exit. 304.
>> 304.
>> Yeah. [music]
>> Sorry, I don't have the Buckyy's exit
memorized just yet, but I'm sure
there'll be a million signs pointing you
to the B exit.
>> You're absolutely right. Got to love
them. Bies.
Hey
Now, if you're coming north from Waco
and you're trying to get to Little River
Academy, it's take exit 304 and then you
can end up on
you can end up on um the loop. Turn left
on the loop and then you can just drive
it straight down. [music]
uh and run right into Little River
Academy.
>> Feel like a lot of this area is just one
big circle on the loop.
Good old Bies.
Like I'm actually kind of hungry. Can we
stop at Bies? Are you guys hungry? Are
you not hungry?
>> I could eat a small
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> Okay. Okay. Well, we'll take you to Bies
for a second cuz we're doing a lot of
video today and
Are they exiting? [music]
>> You're You're exiting.
>> That was right there.
>> That was already there.
What about that one?
>> No, that looks like a bug, though.
>> I hope that's a bug.
>> That looks like a Looks like a little
impact crater.
>> I hope that's not the case.
80°. [music]
So sunny and beautiful.
Just the [music] best company. You know,
Matt,
>> some days I want to heat up a fork until
it's like bright hot and put my eyeballs
out.
>> What are we just talking nonsense?
>> Is that working ass?
>> What are we on right now, Matt? Uh,
we're on the loop. I don't know the
exact highway name, but I refer to it as
the loop.
>> Always the loop. Just everything that
circles around
>> pretty much. [music]
>> Um, Brandon and I were doing some
research the other day and I was Tom was
like, "Do you know that that's actually
not called the loop up by the hospital?"
He's [music] like, "All of us from here
call it the loop."
>> Yep.
>> I'm like, "But it's technically not."
>> Cuz it loops around temple.
>> Yeah. Simple.
>> But you can see it's super pretty out
here. are very rural feel,
but they're doing a lot of development
>> out [music] here
cuz you have
>> Flint Rock.
>> What is this? Flint Rock here.
>> There's Flint Rock and Jubilee in there.
>> Yeah.
>> Is that Knob Creek? And
>> there's also Dear Horton as well.
>> Oh, Dear Horton in there.
>> Dear Horn's in there as well. It's Knob
Creek. Yeah.
Right.
Uh, Oak Ridge
got that completely off. Knob Creek is
right up here a little bit further.
Yeah. [music] And that one's Jubilee
Homes and Flint Rock,
>> but that one back there has Flint
[music] Rock, Dei Horton, and I think a
couple other like local custom spec
builders.
>> Am I staying on loop?
>> You're staying on the loop.
Are you sure about that?
>> I am not.
>> I cuz I feel like that was the exit.
>> That is not the exit. We're going to
Little River Cat. It's straight.
>> Okay.
>> If you take this straight in, you're
you'll run right into it, I think.
>> Yes.
>> So, we're actually going to go into
Little River Academy
and then hang a right on East Main
Street. So, just keep going straight.
You're doing fine.
>> And a right on Maine. I know where
that's that down past my
in-law's house.
>> Yes.
>> So, what's really cool about all these
areas is that well, we're showing you
homes priced around 400,000 this trip,
[music]
or at least that's where we're headed.
>> Yeah.
>> For next week's video. These are
separate videos, but there are homes in
all price points. if you're wanting new
construction or resale. I mean, some of
the ones we just passed are low two, you
know, low twos. Um, there's even a
couple in Troy, uh, that I was
mentioning, the duplexes. I I saw they
just dropped one from 200 to 164.
[music]
Did you see that?
>> Mhm.
>> Hold on.
>> Which is their thing. Yeah. The town
homes.
>> Mhm.
>> But good variety if you want.
>> Yeah. So, this is not pre right here.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Oh, and Lunar, the world is your
oyster for real if you're a buyer right
now because like Matt just mentioned, a
lot of these new communities,
excuse me,
you have your resale and your new
construction
and both are kind of competing with one
another because a lot of these people
with the new with the re I'm sorry, with
the resale homes, [music] they know that
they're competing with new construction.
So, they're trying to give everything
they can just to incentivize you and the
builders have so much that they're
trying to offload. They're throwing
everything at you. You know, your low
interest rates and incentives. And then,
of course, we're able to come on in as
your rep and get you even more.
So, some really [music] So, this is a a
good little point Matt brought up. So,
the the one that we're about to go show
you, it's Academy ISD. So, we didn't
pull up city of academy proper because
there [music] weren't there wasn't any
inventory at 400,000 specifically, but
we know that for a lot of people,
Academy ISD is the priority when looking
for
>> it's almost the entire [music] point.
>> So, because this next one we're going to
is Academy ISD, but it's Temple, its tax
[music] rate is 2.6.
But if you're actually able to get a
home specifically in Academy [music]
under two, I think under two
>> in academy.
>> In Academy
>> probably.
>> Yeah. And then Troy where we just were
that was what 1
>> 68
>> 68. So much lower there. Uh, but
something that we can always verify for
you, you know, on each specific house
[music]
because the huge spread there, like Matt
said, you know, almost a point
difference [music]
in property tax is going to affect your
monthly payment quite a bit.
>> We're we're coming up on uh the Little
River High School. I think this is a
high school. Yeah, the high school. And
so I was looking I looked up the ratings
for academy and they're they're a
B-grade, but it's a 3.58 out of five
on niche.com.
>> That is surprising cuz I feel like a lot
of people want Academy. So that that
rating was actually pretty surprising to
me.
>> I agree.
>> Right.
>> I agree. I [music] bet that they're just
really good people and they actually put
everything in correctly versus other
districts that fluff their numbers.
>> Told me right on Maine.
>> We're turning right on Maine. Now they
they have a couple of small mom and
popod restaurants, gas stations here in
Little River Academy or Academy,
Harvard, whichever one you want to go
with.
So
>> 5 to 7 [music] hopefully that didn't
mess up the concentrate.
>> Yeah, I just realized I want to start
off.
>> But 5 to 7 minutes from [music] I mean
>> temple
>> from temple
10 to
my long 10 minutes from [music]
[snorts]
like the hospitals and HB and all of
that. So nothing. And we have Academy
Middle School here on our right.
>> And then I think this is the elementary
school
>> academy elementary. Just simple as can
be.
>> Yeah.
>> Academy is on that four day school.
>> Oh, that's right. That's a good mention.
She said academy is on a four day job.
High five. Thanks.
>> Thanks.
uh academy is there on a 4 day
school week. So
whether you like that or not, I think
there's [music] going to be some
differing opinions on that
right there. It's like
>> Yeah, it's wide open.
>> This is going to be a a really new
[music] new neighborhood that we're
going into. Looks like there's only
what, four, five, maybe six houses. One,
two, three, four, [music] five, six,
seven. Seven houses. But amazing size
lots. So, if you're looking for
affordable price point with [music] a
very large lot size, this is definitely
something to consider.
All right, so we're pulling in to
the homestead.
Your second entrance. [music]
I got the second.
Pretty peaceful [music] little entrance.
Ember [music]
I assume we're all members. They feel so
much in the police.
>> So, it's going to be on this side.
That [music] one right there.
>> Let's just whip around the neighborhood
real quick.
>> 1924 or 1924.
>> 1924.
>> Welcome back. We are headed up 439 out
to Nolanville to check out our third
final property. [music]
>> Yes.
>> Yes, we are.
>> It's really cool that today we're
getting three entirely different
builders.
And three different areas. So fun.
Is that one not working for you?
>> No.
>> Oh, no. Not this one.
>> So, we pretty much in Nolanville now.
They they've got a mixture of resale and
new build, but they're the vast majority
of the houses out here for sale right
now with the builds.
Um,
do you have I think
elementary school and a middle school
or is it two middle schools?
>> Have to look that up, man.
>> I know there's [music] an elementary
school right there right behind the
Dollar General on 439.
And then we're at a password. [snorts]
See you turn black here.
So, we're headed out to Bella Chararka,
which is their I think that's their only
gated community in that area
>> inville.
Ellara is the only gated community.
>> Yeah,
very upscale. What I like about it is
they've built so [music] many phases in
it.
The front of it is more established
[music] with
still quality pretty homes but more
mature landscaping. And then the the
back phases and homes that are being
built are obviously not as mature but
still you get the new brand spanking new
with all the incentives.
>> Yeah.
>> And they [music] are good right now.
[music]
This morning it was complete cloud
cover. maybe chance of rain. It seemed
by 11:00 we were have the sun poking
through and now I don't see a cloud in
the sky.
Currently 82°
at 2:30 on November 14th. Freaking
[music] November.
left.
>> We're just kind of doing the scenic the
scenic drive here in uh Nolanville.
>> Oh.
>> Um they do have this these awesome
little skate skate ramps.
>> It's existed.
>> Yeah. And then there's a they do have
quite a few different parks. There is a
skate park here in Nanville as well.
There's a couple different kitty parks.
[music] Uh they do have a food truck
court. So on weekends, you'll notice
that there's a couple food charts parked
there and everything is pretty.
>> Have we done a video yet on Nolanville?
I can't recall.
>> I have.
>> So Matt and I both have videos of
Nolanville
in its entirety on our sites.
>> Yeah.
>> And
I'm trying to think what else we got.
What else has No got? got a pretty
awesome like summer 5K series out here,
too.
Um, but it's it's a stones throw away
from Arker Heights and Colleen. [music]
So, the closest grocery store is like 5
minutes away at HB off the Indian Trail.
You're about 15 20 minutes away from
Belton Temple, just depending on where
you're going. Um, [music]
>> we get a lot of people that are looking
to be at Fort Hood out here cuz they
might want to be on the outskirts of
Khen and Harker Heights and so a lot of
people [music] um that are are going
there, but then also you're really not
far from Temple [music]
and the hospitals there either. So kind
of a good middle ground. Feels a little
bit more private.
But Archer Heights has such good food.
>> Yes, Matt. I was just talking about
there's like a new mac and cheese bar.
>> Yeah.
>> And if you don't if you can't tell, I'm
pregnant. And so
>> we're uh I'm a pregnant foodie right now
and he's just a booty. So [music] we're
just talking about the mac and cheese
bar that we need to go check out. But
Parker Heads is great food. I think did
I just see that they closed down um
uh what was that place? [music]
>> I don't know.
>> Had Yeah, you do. I had it that was
Hawaiian uh 8C by the old office. Was it
CH
Hawaiian?
>> Oh, the uh
man, what was the name of that place?
>> Was that not CH Hawaiian?
>> No,
you talking about like the
>> that little drive-thru window right next
to
>> like the the ice place. So, we do have
the one gate for Bella Sharker right
here to the left. I think we should go
through. Do you want to go through
Warriors Legacy?
>> We can. Yeah, let's go through. Oh, I
believe this is prettier, but Okay.
Okay. Warrior's legacy. Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> You got the villas of Bellisara.
[music]
>> And
this is
school, elementary [music] school.
>> Yeah.
>> All it says is
>> I want to know
>> say so they have two elementary schools.
[music] So then you would have to go to
Harker Heights for middle school and
then um
Parker Heights for High School as well.
>> There's a big variety of price points in
this community. So, we're showing you
the $400,000 home,
but [music]
if you want to see a
$700,000 video I did [music] in my video
of Nolanville on my page, I toured a
$700,000 home in the same community. So
that's that's a good comparison. But
really nice that you can live in this
area and and get different price points.
>> So we're like right on the line right
now. We got Harder Heights to the right,
Menville to the left.
And then so [music] Warriors Legacy and
is it the Enclave?
>> What is the name of that subdivision?
>> Enclave.
>> The Enclave. So, we're actually we'll go
in the enclave [music] and then we'll
turn left when it dead end right when it
dead ends and then we'll turn left and
go right into the kind of like the back
eight of uh Ella.
So in the enclave, the houses are
somewhere
>> straight straight.
>> So [music] the bottom stop sign down
there change turn right. Um
I think housing prices are what 3 400k
in this but they're all reselling the
enclave
and then Warriors Legacy is new and it's
what mid 250s up to 400. [music] Mhm.
>> Say that. Yep.
I do want [music] to take you through
Bella Sharka uh on the other way on the
way out so you can see kind of the
difference between [music]
Warriors Legacy and Bellachara.
Did you?
>> No, I didn't.
>> Or did you wash out?
>> Oh, I did not.
>> Neither.
We'll turn left here at this stop
[music] white stop sign.
>> Well, not I don't think I told you happy
Veterans Day the other day.
>> Yeah, you're a horrible person.
>> I love you. Happy Veterans Day.
>> Is that another holiday that you don't
respond to? People text you.
>> Yeah.
>> I just don't I mean I think when I was
in I used to go [music] out and hit like
a restaurant or two. Um
turn [music] right.
So, as you can see from this angle
of the dash cam, so many lots still
available at phases of their building.
>> All right.
>> Bless you.
>> Thank you.
>> You're welcome.
Which one do you really style?
>> Uh, this one's 45.
>> So long. They had back to back showings
on.
>> All right, that wraps up our tour of
three totally different suburbs in the
central Texas area. We [music] started
at Troy, headed on over to Little River
Academy, and we ended up here in
Nolanville, Texas. [music]
But three amazing options in three
totally different vibes, just really
depending on what your overall needs and
wants are.
>> And don't go anywhere because next week
is the good part.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And in the very next video,
we're going to take you on a tour of
three totally different new construction
homes by three very different builders,
all priced [music] at $400,000 in and
around so that you can get a great idea
of [music] what that amount can get you
in each of these suburbs.
>> So, Cors Style Craft and Flint [music]
Rock and you're not going to want to
miss it.
>> No, it's going to be so great. So, stay
tuned for that next video. You're not
going to [music] want to miss it. And if
you are relocating to the central Texas
area, you can find mine and maths
information below. We help people all
the time relocate to and from the
central Texas area. Whether you're
coming over to Fort Hood, you're [music]
looking to be near the hospitals in
Temple, or you're just looking to live
in Central Texas, we're here to help.
[music] Till next time.
>> Till next time.